'use strict';

const questionBank = 
[
  { question : "In what year was the Raven's inaugural season?",
    answer_one: 1996,
    answer_two: 1986,
    answer_three: 1990,
    answer_four: 2001,
    correct_answer: '1996'
  },
  
  { question : "Who were the Ravens first 2 draft picks?",
    answer_one: 'Peter Boulware and Jamie Sharper',
    answer_two: 'Duane Starks and Jim Harbaugh',
    answer_three: 'Chris McAlister and Tony Banks',
    answer_four: 'Jonathon Ogden and Ray Lewis',
    correct_answer: 'Jonathon Ogden and Ray Lewis'
  },
  
  { question : "What was the first stadium the Ravens played in in Baltimore?",
    answer_one: 'M&T Bank Stadium',
    answer_two: 'Oriole Park at Camden Yards',
    answer_three: 'Memorial Stadium',
    answer_four: 'PSI Net Stadium',
    correct_answer: 'Memorial Stadium'
  },

  { question : "How many Head Coaches have the Ravens had?",
    answer_one: 5,
    answer_two: 3,
    answer_three: 2,
    answer_four: 4,
    correct_answer: '3'
  },
  
  { question : "Which 2 Super Bowls did the Ravens win?",
    answer_one: 'XXXV and XLVII',
    answer_two: 'XXX and XXIX',
    answer_three: 'XXXVI and XL',
    answer_four: 'XLV and LI',
    correct_answer: 'XXXV and XLVII'
  },
  
  { question : "Who is the Ravens leader in career touchdowns for a non QB?",
    answer_one: 'Todd Heap',
    answer_two: 'Torrey Smith',
    answer_three: 'Anquan Boldin',
    answer_four: 'Jamal Lewis',
    correct_answer: 'Jamal Lewis'
  },
  
  { question : "What is the Ravens best single season record?",
    answer_one: '15 - 1',
    answer_two: '10 - 6',
    answer_three: '13 - 3',
    answer_four: '11 - 5',
    correct_answer: '13 - 3'
  },
  
  { question : "The Ravens current owner is Steve Bisciotti. Who was the previous owner?",
    answer_one: 'Peter Angelos',
    answer_two: 'Art Modell',
    answer_three: 'Jim Irsay',
    answer_four: 'Jack Kent Cooke',
    correct_answer: 'Art Modell'
  },
  
  { question : "Which former NFL player has served as the Ravens General Manager?",
    answer_one: 'Ozzie Newsome',
    answer_two: 'John Elway',
    answer_three: 'Bill Belichick',
    answer_four: 'Jon Lynch',
    correct_answer: 'Ozzie Newsome'
  },

  { question : "During John Harbaugh's tenure as Head Coach, how many of his assistant coaches have become the Head Coach of a NFL team?",
    answer_one: 8,
    answer_two: 4,
    answer_three: 2,
    answer_four: 6,
    correct_answer: '6'
  },  

];
